

# **NGUYEN VAN PHAT**

# **FRONT-END**

# **CONTACT INFORMATION**

**Sep 20, 1999** 

**\** 0935864032

☑ nguyenvanphat20999@gmail.com

A Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

• https://www.facebook.com/vanphat 304

# **OBJECTIVE**

I'm a front-end developer with 1 year of experience with ReactJs, I can perform coding individually as well as in a team. Have experience working as a developer, and have experience working with a Scrum team. I am willing to learn new technologies and adapt to new challenges. I would like to be a full-stack developer in the future.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### **Programing Languages**

- JavaScript, Typescript
- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- SQL Server, Postgress

#### **Support Library**

- ReactJS, NextJS
- Bootstrap, Tailwind, Antd,
- ReactQuery, React-hook-form, Redux
- NestJs, Express, Prisma, Docker

#### **Source Control**

- GitHub, GitLab

# **Programming Tools**

- Visual studio code- Fork

## Soft skills

# **EDUCATION**

## **University of Food Industry**

**Major: Information system** 

Sep 2019 - 2023

GPA: 3.2/4

#### **Cybersoft**

Major: front-end web

Sep 2019 - 2020

Studyed front-end developer (ReactJs)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **CARP TECH CORPORATION**

Front-end developer

Mar 2022 - Dec 2022

- Project description: VMS is partner information management system includes budgets, vendors, outsourcing staff, report, statements, contracts, payment

#### **IGAP**

Front-end developer

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022

- Project description: A system support delivery and storing between seler and vendor

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Vendor Management System**

Front-end developer

03/2022 - 11/2022

**Customer** ACB bank

**Description** This project is to manage the vendor

of ACB bank and budget forthe projects they want to rent to do

**My position** Front-end Developer

My responsibilities - Analyzing documents

- English reading, listening skill
- Positive attitude
- Observation and catch up quickly
- Ability to work in groups- Listening and learning critiques

# **INTERESTS**

I'm keen on reading manga and IT blogs in my free time and playing other sports like footbal and voleybal

# **HONORS & AWARDS**

#### 2021-2022

3rd place in the talent and creative productcompetition of university

- Develop application functions, make pages: login, vendor ,system config, contract , project, import data, and fix relatedbugs- build and deployment- Ensure that all user i input is validated before submitting it toBack-end

## **Technologies used**

- Languages: HTML5, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript.

- Library: ReactJS, React-query, Ant Design- Browser: IE, Chrome, Safari, Edge

## **Delivery Management System**

Front-end developer

10/2021 - 3/2022

Customer: IGAP

**Description** This project is to manage and

support delivery and storingbetween

seller and vendor

My position Front-end Developer

My responsibilities

 Analyzing documents- Develop application functions: split update order, userpermission, and fix related bugs- Ensure that all user input is validated before submitting

it toBack-end

**Technologies used** 

- Languages: HTML5 , CSS,

JavaScript.

- Library: ReactJS, Redux-saga, Ant Design- Browser: IE, Chrome, Safari,

Edge